<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sections on Jonathan Old</title>
    <link>/sections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sections on Jonathan Old</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/sections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my website. I am an Predoc with STICERD at the LSE, working with Robin Burgess and Oriana Bandiera. I am interested in political economy and development economics, and have previously worked on conflict and political reservations in India, democratic transitions and state repression, and longevity.
I plan to start a PhD in Economics in Fall 2021.
Curriculum Vitae (Version November 2020)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email: j.d.old@lse.ac.uk
Twitter: @Jonathan_Old
Github: jonathanold</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/other-papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/other-papers/</guid>
      <description>Preservation or degradation? Communal management and ecological change in a southeast Michigan forest, with Fred Nelson, Elisa Collins, Alain Frechette, Cynthia Koenig, Mosé Jones-Yellin, Brihannala Morgan, Gita Ramsay, and Claudia Rodriguez, Biodiversity and Conservation, October 2008, Volume 17, Issue 11, pp 2757-2772</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/personal/</guid>
      <description>Test pic
Fearless Sidekick - Kirby passed in Aug 2016
Website: I cloned the website from Gautam Rao. Please feel welcome to use and re-purpose the code for the website, which you can find at my GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/projects/</guid>
      <description>I have several projects with PhD students at HZDR.
 This website is cloned from Gautam Rao. You can find the source code on my Github repository. Please feel free to copy it for your own website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
